怎么了，老板？我是罗尼·沈。
What's up, boss? I'm Ronnie Shen.
然后我是迈克尔·科斯塔。这是《体育战争》，一个我们法律上不允许彼此同意的节目。
Then I'm Michael Costa. This is Sports War, the show where we are legally not allowed to agree with each other.
比如说，如果我说UFC需要更暴力……
For example, if I say UFC needs to be more violent...
哦，那我就说拳手们应该通过持证治疗师和平解决分歧。
Oh, well, then I say fighters need to sell a difference as peacefully with a licensed therapist.
是吗？那我来介绍一下我的两位治疗师，西格蒙德·弗洛伊德和卡尔·荣格。
Yeah, well, I'd like to introduce you to my two therapists, Sigmund Freud and Carl Jung.
哦，是吗？那我也应该去治疗一下。
Oh, yeah? Well, I should go to therapy.
看看，我就是这么迷恋你妈的。
See, that's how I'm obsessed with your mom.
对。
Yeah.
是啊，伙计，没错。你需要和持证的医疗专业人士探讨这些感受。
Yeah, man, exactly. You need to explore those feelings with a licensed medical professional.
我会给你推荐一些名字。
I'll send you some names.
嘿，我们来聊聊高尔夫吧，好吗？
Hey, let's talk golf, okay?
短杆、业余、差点、球洗机。
Short game, amateur, handicap, ball washer.
这些不仅仅是罗尼的绰号。
These aren't just Ronnie's nicknames.
它们还是高尔夫术语。
They're golf terms.
而本周是高尔夫球场上的历史性一周。
And this week was a historic one on the links.
今晚，罗里·麦克艾沃伊成为仅有的六位赢得所有四大高尔夫锦标赛的球员之一，首次赢得大师赛冠军。
Tonight, Rory McAvoy is now one of only six golfers to win all four major golf championships, winning the Masters for the first time.
这个在北爱尔兰长大的孩子……
The kid who grew up in Northern Ireland...
……满怀激动，赢得了他的第一件绿夹克，这是他在赢得上一次大满贯冠军11年之后的成就。
...overcome with emotion, winning his first green jacket, 11 years, after winning his last major championship.
哇，恭喜罗里·麦克艾沃伊。
Wow, congrats to Roy McAvoy.
他花了11年才拿到一件新的绿色西装外套。
It took him 11 years to get a new green blazer.
作为一个目前被男士服装店禁足20年的人，我完全能感同身受。
And as someone currently serving a 20-year band from the men's warehouse, I can totally relate.
这完全不一样，你这个白痴。
This is totally different, you idiot.
罗里试图完成的是体育界最难的事情之一。
Rory was trying to accomplish one of the hottest things in all of sports.
而你只是跑到试衣间里拉了一泡屎。
You just took a dump in a fitting room.
好吧，他们保证我会喜欢我的穿着，而打破口头合同是要付出代价的。
Well, they guaranteed I was going to like the way I looked and breaking a verbal contract has consequences.
重点是，我为罗里·麦克艾沃伊感到高兴。
The point is, I'm happy for Roy McAvoy.
哦，是吗？好吧，我不高兴。
Oh, yeah? Well, I'm not.
好吗？我不想表现得很高兴。
Okay? I don't want to seem happy.
大家都知道，爱尔兰人只有在抑郁的时候才是最棒的。
Everyone knows that Irish people are the best when they're depressed.
你难道没读过詹姆斯·乔伊斯吗？
Haven't you ever read James Joyce?
当然没有，我是弗兰克·麦考特的粉丝。
Hell, no, I'm a Frank McCourt man.
他是爱尔兰裔美国人，蠢货。
Well, he's Irish American dumbass.
查查你的数据，兄弟。
Check your stats, bro.
麦考特是在利默里克的贫民窟长大的，他以一种自威廉·巴特勒·叶芝以来无人能及的方式触及了爱尔兰苦难的灵魂，蠢货，这让我们想起了爱尔兰眼泪的夜晚。
McCourt was raised in the slums of Limerick and he spoke to the soul of Irish suffering like no man since William Butler Yates, dumbass, which brings to our eyes Irish eyes better than night.
接下来是什么会让罗里·麦克艾沃伊在公众场合哭泣？
What will make Roy McAvoy cry in public next?
一如既往，由赌博赞助。
As always, brought to you by gambling.
赌博。
Gambling.
你真正上瘾的只是享受美好时光。
The only thing you're really addicted to is having a good time.
继续前进。
You're moving on.
NBA季后赛周六开始。
The NBA Playoff starts Saturday.
但如果你是一个像科斯塔一样有着丰富想象力的小女孩，你也有理由感到兴奋。
But if you're a little girl with a big imagination like Costa, you also have a reason to be excited.
让开，肯。
Move over Ken.
勒布朗·詹姆斯成为第一个加入新肯大使系列的男性运动员。
LeBron James is a first male athlete to be part of the new Ken Basseter line.
还有芭比娃娃，看看他。
And Barbie dolls, look at him.
盒子背面的信息写着：“真正的MVP。”
The message on the back of the box says, a true MVP.
“我们的勒布朗·詹姆斯肯大使娃娃代表了阿克伦市的韧性、希望和自豪。”
Our LeBron James Ken Basseter's doll represents resilience, hope, and pride for the city of Akron.
这是最蠢的玩具。
This is the dumbest toy ever.
我希望它配有一个布朗尼·詹姆斯娃娃，你会强迫他玩，即使他很烂。
I hope it comes of a brony James doll that you'll force to play with even though it sucks.
好吧，布朗尼又来了，男孩，玩具。
Well, brawn again, boy, toy.
我恰好喜欢勒布朗。
I happen to love LeBron.
他拥有每个小女孩想要的玩偶的一切。
He has every, he has what every little girl wants in a doll.
对阿克伦市的自豪感。
Pride for the city of Akron.
现在，他们可以尽情地和一个穿着像14岁少年的中年男人玩耍，没有任何意见。
Now, they can play until their hearts content with a middle-aged man dressed like a 14-year-old no notes.
他们应该把这个系列扩展到其他NBA传奇人物，比如丹尼斯·罗德曼，“蠕虫”，芭比历史上第一个有穿孔阴囊的玩偶。
They should expand this to other NBA legends, like Dennis Rodman, The Worm, The First Doll in Barbie history with the piercable scrotum.
或者我童年最喜欢的，威尔特·张伯伦。
Or my favorite, my favorite from the childhood, Will Chamberlain.
有成百上千种不同的芭比，他可以和所有的芭比发生关系。
There are hundreds of different Barbies and he can have sex with all of them.
这让我们来到了本周的“极其随机代言交易”，由乔安娜面料公司赞助。
Which brings us to our extremely random endorsement deal Better the Week, presented by Joanne Fabrics.
哪个运动员会签下下一个极其随机的代言交易？由赌博赞助。
Which athlete will sign the next extremely random endorsement deal brought to you by Gambley.
赌博，他们现在在轮椅上做了惊人的事情。
Gambley, they're doing amazing things with wheelchair now.
来看棒球吧。
Look, let's go to the diamond.
棒球是一项你必须了解手势的运动，对吧？
Baseball is a sport where you have to know your signs, right?
曲球，换投。
Curveball, pitching change.
我要四杯啤酒，不给小费。
I'll take four beers, no tip.
但本周，布莱斯·哈珀把这提升到了一个新高度。
But this week, Bryce Harper took that to the next level.
费城费城人队的重炮手布莱斯·哈珀即将再次迎来父亲身份。
Philadelphia Philly slugged her Bryce Harper is about to take another swing at Fatherhood.
他在昨晚的比赛中用创意揭示了宝宝的性别。
And he got creative with the babies' baby's gender revealed during last ninths game.
哈珀让特雷·特纳递给他一根蓝色或粉色的球棒，然后他上场击球，揭示了性别。
Harper Ashford stopped trade turner to hand him either a bluer-a-pink bat before he went up to head as a gender reveal.
他在上场击球前得知，他将迎来一个男孩。
He found out right before he stepped up to the plate that he'll be having a baby boy.
这太棒了。
This is awesome.
棒球需要更多的医疗测试在比赛中揭示。
Baseball needs more medical tests revealed during games.
我想看到一个跑者滑进本垒，裁判大喊：
I want to see a runner slide into home in the Empire of Yells.
“你安全了，免于性病。”
You are safe from Tasex disease.
科斯塔，你简直疯了，好吗？
Costner, you're out of your f***ing mind, all right?
这毁了比赛。
This is ruining the game.
你不能在击球时做性别揭示。
You can't be doing gender reveals at the plate.
性别揭示应该是为了一小群你希望用爆炸物伤害的亲密朋友。
Gender reveals are supposed to be for a close group of loved ones that you're hoping to injure with explosives.
罗尼，我这里有你的性别揭示棒。
Ronnie, I got your gender reveal bat right here.
惊喜，它是棕色的，因为你是个混蛋。
Surprise, it's brown since you're a piece of shit.
好吧，科斯塔。
Well, costner.
是的。
Yeah.
对于我们这些有过性生活的人来说，这是个灾难，好吗？
For those of us who've had sex, this is a disaster, all right?
棒球是你在不想让某人怀孕时想到的事情。
Baseball is the thing you think about when you're not trying to get someone pregnant.
把你的家庭计划从我的体育中拿开，好吗？
Get your family planning out of my sports, okay?
我们能不能看到一个和性无关的棒球故事？
Can we please see a baseball story that has nothing to do with sex?
巴尔的摩金莺队的双A附属球队切萨皮克湾牛队决定推出一个替代队名，以吸引新的观众。
The Baltimore Orioles double-a affiliate that chest-of-peak base-ox decided to unveil an alternative team identity to help them gain traction with new audiences.
包括新的替代名字“牡蛎捕手”，以及一个全新的标志。
That included the new alternative name, the Oyster Catchers, along with a brand new logo.
这个标志，至少对许多人来说，似乎描绘了一个棒球手套抓住了一只牡蛎，而其他人则有不同的解读。
This logo, which at least to many seems to depict a baseball glove catching an Oyster, others interpreted a bit differently.
球队认真对待了批评，在几分钟内删除了他们的公告，但后来他们推出了一个新的标志，显示一只鸟拿着一根球棒。
The team took the criticisms to heart, deleting their unannouncedment within minutes, but later they unveiled a new new logo showing a bird holding a bat.
该死的。
God dammit.
我再也不能用棒球手套偷偷藏牡蛎了。
I'm never going to be able to slip and all you stuff of baseball glove ever again.
而这是我唯一喜欢它们的方式。
And that's the only way I like them.
你在说什么，罗尼？
What are you talking about, Ronnie?
牡蛎标志很棒。
The Oyster logo is great.
如果有的话，新标志才是变态的。
If anything, the new logo is the one that's perverted.
那只鸟显然是叼着某个家伙被切下来的丁丁飞走了。
That bird is clearly flying away with some guy severed penis.
你知道吗？那可怜的家伙。
And you know what? That poor guy.
但那些幸运的小鸟宝宝，真是一顿美餐。
But those lucky baby birds, what a lunch.
这整个事情只是证实了我的信念，棒球队应该完全取消标志，好吗？
This whole thing just confirms my belief that baseball team should get rid of logos entirely, okay?
如果他们不是在性化牡蛎，就是在激怒原住民。每支球队都应该只用他们的城市命名，比如费城费城人队，波士顿波士顿人队，克利夫兰克利夫兰人队，底特律乳房队。
If they're not sexualizing oysters that pissing off Native Americans, every team should just name themselves after their city, like a Philadelphia Phillies, the Boston-Bostonese, the Cleveland-Clevelandese, the Detroit-Titties.
没有任何性暗示，好吗？
Nothing sexual, okay?
我不同意，罗尼。
I disagree, Ron.
所有球队名字都应该是性化的，但要有教育意义。
All team names should be sexual, but educational.
这个国家的性教育简直是个笑话。
Sex ed in this country is a joke.
但如果费城输卵管队对阵克利夫兰蒸汽机队，那么我们就学到了东西。
But if the Philadelphia Philopian tubes play the Cleveland steamers, well now we're learning, which brings us to our four-carat diamond better the week.
这让我们来到了本周的“4克拉钻石”最佳预测。
What baseball mascot will Ronnie have a dream about tonight?
今晚罗尼会梦到哪个棒球吉祥物？由赌博赞助。
Brought to you by gambling.
赌博。
Gambling.
许多文化都喜欢在户外睡觉。
Tons of cultures sleep outside.
好了，这就是《体育战争》。
All right, that's it for sportswear.
下次加入我们时，我们将讨论贾·莫兰特在下一个庆祝动作中应该模仿什么战争行为。
Join us next time when we debate what act of war, Jean-Marant, will should mine for his next celebration.
一定是按下核按钮，伙计。
It's gotta be hitting a nuclear button, man.
我要按那个按钮。
I'm gonna hit that button.
这是一场平局。
This is a draw.